freemarriage.com 2006-06-18

# BizHat.com - Privacy Policy

BizHat.com is strongly committed to honoring the privacy of our visitors. This privacy statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site (http://www.BizHat.com).

**Information Collection and Use**  
BizHat.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

**Cookies**  
The cookie is a piece of computer software that communicates between visitors computer and the server (computer). Cookies are used by our banner rotation software (scripts) to record the impressions, click throughs and to make sure visitors don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to visitors interests, and to save visitors login information (for message board etc) so that they don't have to re-enter it each time they visit our site. We do not use cookies to record user behaviour or to collect any personal information on our visitors. We work with various third party advertising networks and their ads may contain cookies. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing**  
We will share aggregated demographic information (e.g. 60 % of our visitors are from India) with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**Partner Sites**  
BizHat.com can not be held responsible for information collected by our partner sites and for information (personal or otherwise) provided by BizHat.com visitors voluntarily to our partner sites. Please note that some of our partner sites are co-branded but their privacy statement may differ from ours. We encourage our visitors to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Public Forums**  
This site makes fan clubs, chat rooms, opinion polls and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and users/visitors should exercise caution when deciding to disclose their personal information. Information posted in public areas may be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties.

**Newsletter**  
If a visitor wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask only for email address. However, those who subscribe to our newsletter have the choice of unsubscribing at will without any intervention on our part. E-mail addresses/ids collected by our newsletter software are never shared with any third party.

**Referral Service**  
If a visitor elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. BizHat.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. BizHat.com does not store the email addresses of the persons used in this process.

**External Links**  
BizHat.com provides a Web Directory to visitors which contains links to other sites. BizHat.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of linked Web sites. We encourage visitors to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their policies may differ from ours.
